Cherry：Do we wait here?
Cherry：여기서 기다려?
Xenon：Yes. Why did you accompany me here anyway?
Xenon：그래. 대체 뭐하러 따라 온거야?
Cherry：Hey, I took part in the Boss fight; make sense that I get to rescue the princess, right? I want to see NEKO in person as well.
Cherry：내가 이미 Boss를 쓰러뜨렸잖아. 이제 공주만 구해내면 되겠네. 그리고 나도 한 번쯤은 NEKO 만나보고 싶었거든.
Xenon：... Princess? I say more pixie than princess.
Xenon：……공주는 무슨. 요괴겠지.
Cherry：You are so mean~ She's a cute girl. isn't she?
Cherry：하여간 진짜. 그게 여자애한테 할 소리야??
Xenon：Umm... She's... unique, to say the least. Be prepared when you see her.
Xenon：하아…… 아무튼 굉장히 특이한 녀석이니깐... 너도 마음의 준비를 해 둬.
Cherry：All this talk is making me even more interested to see her!
Cherry：그렇게 말하니깐 더 만나보고 싶어졌어!
Cherry：On a side note, that's a serious crowd down there at the main entrance.
Cherry：그런데 방금 아래 정문 쪽에 사람들이 엄청 몰려온 것 같던데.
Cherry：Good thing you had friends that could let us in through the back door. I thought we're gonna get stuck outside.
Cherry：네 친구가 우리를 후문으로 안내해줬기에 망정이지, 절대 못들어 올 줄 알았는데.
Cherry：Didn't you say that the admins have been watching you closely?
Cherry：관리국의 감시가 엄청 심해졌다고 말하지 않았어?
Xenon：I still have my connections over here. If not, I wouldn't know any of this in the first place.
Xenon：이 근처에도 몇 사람들이 몰려 오더군. 안그랬으면 나도 이쪽으로 들어올 생각을 못했겠지.
Cherry：Wow, so a shut-in like you actually made "friends"...
Cherry：...너처럼 자폐아 같은 애도 친구를 사귈 수 있다니....
Xenon：You... it's all thanks to them that the evidence I provided could actually influence the investigation.
Xenon：이봐…… 다행히 저 사람들 덕분에 내가 모아둔 증거로 조사 방향을 돌릴수 있었던 거라고.
Xenon：... Ah, we should stop chatting here.
Xenon：……하아, 여기선 그런 얘긴 그만 두자.
[>>>Fast Forward>>>]
[>>>빨리 감기>>>]
Xenon：Hey. Over here.
Xenon：이봐. 여기라고.
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Ehhh? Why are you the one to come and get me? Where are my dad and others?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：어랏? 왜 네가 데리러 온거야? 아빠는?
Xenon： I notify them to wait at home. There are still some procedures to go through.
Xenon：집에서 기다리고 계시라고 전했다. 그리고 아직 수속해야 할 일들이 좀 남아있다고.
Xenon：You probably have no idea why you are released, right?
Xenon：네가 왜 갑자기 이렇게 풀려났는지 아직도 잘 모르겠지?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Dude, I don't even know why I was arrested in the first place! It's utterly ridiculous!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：아니 난 아직도 왜 내가 갑자기 잡혀갔는지도 잘 모르겠다구! 진짜 황당 그 자체!
Xenon：You don't remember, do you...? That makes it even harder to explain things clearly.
Xenon：기억이 안나는 건가?……？설명하기 더 복잡해졌군.
NEKO#ΦωΦ：...... Who's that behind you?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：…… 뒤에 저 사람은?
Cherry：Hi~
Cherry：안녕~
NEKO#ΦωΦ：EHHH!? It's Cherry! OH MY ****** GOD!!!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：우옷!? Cherry잖아!? 우와아!!
Cherry：Eh? You recognize me?
Cherry：응? 날 알고 있어?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Of course! NEKO is a big fan of yours! Why are you here!?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：NEKO는 당신 팬이라구! 어떻게 여기에 있는 거지!?
Xenon：She's half the reason why you could be released.
Xenon：네가 이렇게 나올 수 있던 것도, 반 정도는 쟤 도움이었어.
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Huh? What does that mean? Hmm??
NEKO#ΦωΦ：응? 무슨 소리야 그게? 으응??
Xenon：It's a long story... All in all, we should leave here before we get any attention. Let's go.
Xenon：말하자면 좀 길어…… 아무튼 더욱 주의를 끌기 전에 빨리 여길 떠나자고. 가자.
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Come on~ tell me what's going on~
NEKO#ΦωΦ：으아아앙～～빨리 제대로 설명해 줘!
Xenon：You are so noisy... I'll tell you once we leave here.
Xenon：시끄러워 죽겠군…… 길에서 천천히 말해주도록 할게.
Xenon：There's a **** ton of people at the main entrance ready to engulf you. Keep your head down.
Xenon：정문에 너 때문에 온 사람들이 널려있다고. 고개를 숙여.
[Signal Lost]
[신호 중단]